{
    "id": "cfaad813c6244bb9bfe4d5ff702fb7a4",
    "title": "Special Uses Of Adjectives",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "bd918144ad5841fe8cea11e179f729d5",
            "title": "Special Uses Of Adjectives",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. are not always cowards.",
                    "description": "When an adjective is used to denote a class of people, it is always used with the. The cautious means the same as cautious people. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Cautious",
                        "The cautious",
                        "Cautious people"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The richest ……………………….. not always the happiest.",
                    "description": "Adjectives used to denote a class of persons are always plural and take the plural verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Blessed as ……………………….",
                    "description": "When an adjective is used to denote a class of people, it is always used with the.",
                    "answers": [
                        "meek",
                        "the meek",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. is uncertain.",
                    "description": "Sometimes adjectives are used to denote some abstract quality. In this case also they are used with the article the.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Future",
                        "The future",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………. we know nothing.",
                    "description": "No article is used in this expression.",
                    "answers": [
                        "In short",
                        "In the short"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I must have the terms down in ……………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "the black and white",
                        "black and white"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am afraid his situation is going from ………………………..",
                    "description": "No articles are used in these expressions",
                    "answers": [
                        "bad to worse",
                        "the bad to worse"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The unemployed ……………………….. losing hope.",
                    "description": "When the + adjective refers to a well-known group of people, it is plural.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The government should do something to solve …………………………",
                    "description": "These expressions cannot be used with the possessive ’s.",
                    "answers": [
                        "the poor's problems",
                        "poor people's problems",
                        "the problems of the poor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am ………………………… in my family.",
                    "description": "Superlatives are often used without a noun if the meaning is clear.",
                    "answers": [
                        "the shortest",
                        "the shortest person",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can’t afford ………………………….",
                    "description": "The correct structure is that + adjective /adverb + article + noun",
                    "answers": [
                        "that a big car",
                        "that big a car",
                        "that big car"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… is she?",
                    "description": "The correct structure is how + adjective / adverb + a/an + noun. Note that the article goes after the noun in this special structure.",
                    "answers": [
                        "How good a dancer",
                        "How good dancer",
                        "How a good dancer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}